# **LEITH PRICE**

Brisbane, QLD 4503 (+61) 421 547 423 leith.price@gmail.com

#### **GitHub**

https://github.com/ LeithPrice

### Linkedin

https:// www.linkedin.com/in/ leithprice/

# **Programming Languages**

HTML 5 CSS (SASS) JAVASCRIPT RUBY

## **Technologies**

React.JS RoR (RAILS) Node.JS PostgreSQL

### **Professional skills**

GitHub - Branching Agile Wire framing Responsive design

#### **PROFILE**

I have owned and run a successful business for 18 years which started from small truck subcontracting to national logistics companies and expanding up to a 24/7 large interstate fleet. I have relished and thrived in the challenges my businesses have presented. My ability to knuckle down and get the job done under pressure have honed my skills to make accurate decisions in an environment where attention to detail is paramount.

Having partially completed a BSc(Com) in 2002, I have always had an avid interest and passion for computer science and took the opportunity to further my knowledge and experience by embarking on a Diploma of IT to achieve my goal of becoming a Software developer.

Looking beyond my technical training I believe my focus, drive to learn, and commitment will make me an asset to any business willing to give me an opportunity.

I am a committed family man, father of 2 and dedicated worker and enjoy doing landscaping jobs around the house in my spare time.

#### **EXPERIENCE**

# Full Stack Developer Student, Coder Academy; -2022 - Present

I will complete my studies in the Diploma of IT at the end of November, 2022. The course content, which is mainly project - based, has trained me in multiple programming languages, multiple frameworks and accepted workplace practices.

Class
Foundation Programming [CA22022CMP1041-B.B]
Introduction to Web [CA22022INT1012-B.B]
Programming I [CA22022PRG1002-B.B]
Database Systems [CA52022PRG1048-B.A]
Discrete Mathematics [CA52022PRG1010-B.A]
Information Systems [CA52022CMP1042-B.A]
Programming II [CA72022PRG1006-B.A]
Introduction to Software Engineering [CA72022CMP1043-B.A]

# Self-Employed Mechanic, Maxwell Tyre and Mechanical; - 2016 -

#### Present

Currently self employed running my own mobile mechanical and auto electrical business. This role involves many transferable skills to the world of IT.

I work closely with the client taking the time to understand what they want to achieve. I use my technical skills to diagnose the issue with the vehicle and prepare a solution. I explain a fairly technical solution to the layman customer.

As this is my own business, my tasks are completed independent of assistance, and if I require more information I have the skills to find the resources I need to achieve the desired technical result. My commitment to excellence and ability to communicate with customers can be reinforced by my current Google reviews rating of 4.9 starts over 200 individual reviews. https://g.page/maxwelltyre\_mechanical?share

# Managing Director, PRT; —2013 - 2016

PRT had the rail delivery contract for Aurizon Cairns and as a part owner of PRT, I was involved in the allocation of workloads, hiring of staff, enforcing legal compliance and monitoring the ongoing maintenance of the 6 full truck-trailer fleet.

We concurrently owned and managed 10 interstate refrigerated b-doubles truck-trailer sets based out of Brisbane that transported freight and produce all over Australia. This extreme and varied workload perfected my ability to manage large staff environments, communicate clearly and confidently with Top-Tier clients, plan ahead and manage the company and my workload.

In my time at PRT, my most important and regularly used skills were problem resolution, attention to detail, being efficient with my time and an understanding of cost of operation and labour vs return from a business point of view.

# Managing Director, ADIP Investments Pty Ltd; — 2005 - 2016

ADIP Investments was a trading company used for my contracting work as a Transport Freight Provider. Providing Transport services to Top-Tier clients such as Toll Group and Linfox. This role allowed me to develop my work ethic and commitment to the ethos of "not finishing till the job is done"

Working long hours, with large work loads, completely autonomously, I understood the need to take responsibility for my workload. I am proud to have developed the ability to both have tunnel vision to focus on the task at hand but also the ability to multi-task across a spectrum of responsibilities.

#### **EDUCATION**

Coder Academy — Diploma of IT, 2022 (To be completed Nov 28th)
Work Skills — Cert 3 in Automotive Electrical Technology, 2021
Work Skills — Cert 2 in Automotive Air Conditioning Technology, 2020
Work Skills — Cert 3 in Heavy Vehicle Mechanical Technology, 2020

USQ — Bachelor of Science (Computing) - Incomplete(12 of 24 units completed) 2001-2002

Karratha SHS — Year 12 High School Completion Cert, 1999

# **REFERENCES**

References available upon request.